# ITAI MIZLISH

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT



054-2258899



itaim148@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/itai-mizlish/



https://github.com/itaim18



www.itaimiz.com

## EDUCATION

Bachelor in Science in 2015-2019 **Computer Science** 

JCT Lev Academic Center

#### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript & ES6
- React
- Sass
- Node.js
- Firebase
- · MongoDB (mongoose and studio 3T).
- express
- Responsive design
- Tailwind

#### LANGUAGES

English



Hebrew

#### PROFILE

I am a highly motivated Front-end Developer and web developer with a strong understanding of React.js, its methods and hooks. Experienced in building front-end and full-stack architectures from scratch. Proficient in UI/UX through CSS tools (Sass, Tailwind, Bootstrap). Learned DS implementation and algorithms solving in JavaScript and ES6. A Computer Science graduate in highschool and a self learner.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Front-End Developer**

2022 - present

- · Designed and created architectures for web applications
- · Developed fullstack web apps using MERN structure and firebase.
- Using Javascript libraries in CSS and SASS to create user interfaces.
- · Experienced in functional programming in Javascript and knowledgeable in ES6.

2016-2018 **Tutor** 

Israeli Center for Advancement in Math (associated with Bar Ilan University)

- · Facilitated annual Science Day activities for children.
- Tutored basic Physics and Aeronautics lessons in schools in the TA Metropolitan Area.
- Graded tests and tutored children with special needs.

## Military Service

2019-2022

Infantry Unit

# Volunteering

2015-2018

Krembo Wings

· Assisted and accompanied children with special needs and formed unique connections with them.

# CERTIFICATES

The complete 2022 Web development Bootcamp | Udemy

| Udemy

**React - The Complete Guide** 

**JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass** 

| Udemy